养鬼吃人
主演：安德鲁.罗宾逊
主演：克莱尔.希金丝
主演：肖恩.查普曼
导演：克莱夫.巴克
你想要什么呢？科顿先生
What's your pleasure, Mr. Cotton?
盒子
The box.
拿着吧,这是你的
Take it, it's yours.
他永远属于你
It always was.
这就是其中的一处房产
It's gotta be one of these.
我都快冻死了
I'm going to freeze to death.
- 好了 好了 - 也许有人把锁换了．
-Okay, okay. -Well, maybe somebody changed the lock.
谁？是谁把锁换掉了呢？
Like who? Who's gonna change this lock?
噢,我也不知道. 我只是瞎猜的
Well, I don't know. It was just a suggestion.
噢,成了
Ah. Success.
瞧
Voila.
对了,就是这里
Well, this is it--
我家的旧家产
the old homestead.
噢,很潮湿的味道
Yuck. It smells damp.
对了,它已经.... 空了很长一段时间了 不是吗？
Well, it's... been empty for a while, hasn't it?
但很快可以使它热闹起来
But we'll soon warm it up
使它有家的感觉
and get it feeling like a home.
你在这儿呆了多久呢？
How long since you were here?
噢,最美好的十年,在此度过
Oh, the better part of 10 years.
我前妻去世后, 我想把它卖掉
I wanted to sell it after the old lady died,
但我弟弟弗兰克不同意.
but I couldn't get Frank to agree.
我想他需要个 避风港之类的地方
I guess he needed a hideout or something.
你能来看看这个吗？
Would you look at this?
别担心
And don't worry,
对我来说这些没有半点意义
this stuff means nothing to me.
已是过去了
It all goes.
我想半数家产属于你兄弟的吧
I thought half of it was your brother's.
他只知道浪费光阴 真是不成才, 另外...
I've never known him to kick cash out of bed. Besides...
他可能正在什么酒吧大醉酩酊呢
he's probably behind bars someplace.
你得知道
You know...
在我们对它整理前, 得让克里斯蒂看看这个地方
we have to let Kirsty see this place before we do a thing to it.
她会喜欢
She'll love it.
你真的想搬到这儿来吗？
You really want to move in here?
你不喜欢它吗？
You don't like it?
我想这比布鲁克林好多了
I suppose it's better than Brooklyn.
噢,别开始,朱莉娅.
Oh, don't start, Julia.
- 什么别开始？ - 听着
-Don't start what? -Look.
我们可以在这儿住下来
We can make it work here.
我的事业做得很出色. 你可以做点自己喜欢的事
Now I've got a terrific job, you're back on your own turf--
我们会很幸福.
we can be happy.
- 好了 好了 - 那吵什么呢？
-All right, all right. -So what's the argument?
- 没有争吵啊 - 噢 我的上帝．
-No argument. -Oh, Christ!
亲爱的
Honey...
他妈的
Shit.
拉里. 拉里
Larry! Larry!
- 你在哪儿呢？ - 在这儿
-Where are you? -In here.
有人在这儿住过吗？
Squatters?
是弗兰克.
Frank.
- 他在这儿住吗？ - 噢 他以前曾在过这儿
-He's here? -Well, he's been here.
我是说我看见厨房里还留着些 他的稀奇古怪的东西
I mean, there's stuff in the kitchen you wouldn't believe.
很明显,他又跑掉了
He's obviously made one of his famous getaways.
会是谁的电话呢？
What the hell is that?
是谁？
-Who is this?
爸爸吗？
Dad.
克里斯蒂!
Kirsty!
我成功了
I got through.
你在哪儿呢？
Barely. Where are you?
我找到了房子．
I found a room.
- 你说什么？ - 我说 我找到了房子住
-You what? -I said, I found a room.
等等,我以为你暂时 会跟我们住一起
Wait, I thought you were going to stay with us for a while
爸爸
Dad.
你会喜欢这所房子.
Well, you'd like this house.
你会喜欢我的房子的
You'd like my room.
我真的很想让你来 看看这房子.真的很棒
I'd really like you to see this house. It's something else.
也许在接下来的几天中 我会找份工作
Maybe in the next couple of days. I gotta find myself a job.
为什么呢？甜心
What for, sweetie?
我说你架子摆够了吧, 没必要这样
Look, you've already made the gesture, there's no need--
爸,不是摆架子, 这是我必须做的事情
Dad, this isn't a gesture. This is something I need to do.
稍微信任我一下吧,好吗？
Come on and trust me a little, okay?
明天给我回电话 我会的,我会去见你
-Call me tomorrow. -I will. I'll see you.
再见了,爸爸
Bye, Dad.
你觉得怎么样？
So?
为什么不搬进来呢？
Why not?
太棒了.
Great.
我们会在周日搬进来
We'll move in on Sunday.
听着,通过这个地方时 不能碰坏了它的表面
Listen, look out for the moulding on the way through here.
- 好的 - 好的
- All right. - All right.
- 你能向后拉下吗？ - 当然
- Are you all right back there? -Yeah yeah.
对.好了.直接把它搬到楼上去
All right, okay. Now just take it straight up the stairs.
别担心.可以通过去
Don't worry, it'll get through.
- 好的．什么情况？ - 夹着我的手臂了！
-All right. What's the matter? -Hey, you got my arm!
好的 好的
- All right, all right. -Oh, God.
当心
-(Man)Watch it. -(Larry)Oh.
我们休息一下吧,伙计们
Let's take five, guys.
你那儿收拾的怎么样了？
How's things in there?
房间里像掉进了炸弹一样乱七八糟
Looks like a bomb dropped.
有啤酒吗？
You got any beer?
冰箱里有一些
There's some in the fridge.
噢,不错
Oh, well...
为什么不拿些啤酒来喝呢？
why don't I get it?
对我来说,没有比这更爽的事儿了
I've got nothing better to do.
抱歉打扰一下
Excuse me.
- 真是幸运的一天喔． - 嘿
-My lucky day. -Hi.
- 你想买张床吗？ - 不是很想
-Do you wanna buy a bed? -Not much.
爸爸！
Dad?
- 克里斯蒂 - 嘿！
- Kirsty! -Hi.
哈罗,甜心,到这儿来
Hello, sweetie. Come here.
- 你们先歇会儿． - 噢 好的
-Here you go. -(Man)Oh, great.
这房子真大.
This is a big house.
- 你喜欢吗？ - 是的
-You like? -Yeah.
我喜欢
Me like.
如果我们能把这该死的床搬过去 我愿意带你参观一番
Ill give you the grand tour if we ever get this goddamn bed moved.
- 朱莉娅在这儿吗？ - 她在楼上
-Is Julia here? -She's upstairs.
注意,对她温和点儿,好吗？
Look, be gentle with her, okay?
- 她讨厌搬家． - 真让人惊讶
-She hates moving. -Surprise.
- 克里斯蒂． - 好啦 我会乖点
-Kirsty. -Okay, all right. I'll be nice.
你们继续做这累人的活儿吧
You get on with the grunt work
- 我得喝点儿咖啡． - 好主意
-and I'll make myself some coffee. -That's a great idea.
- 厨房在那儿． - 好的
-There's the kitchen. -Okay.
再见
Bye.
那是你女儿吗？
-Is that your daughter? -Uh-huh.
- 很像她妈妈． - 她妈妈已经过世了
-Got her mother's looks. -Her mother's dead.
拜托！
Come on.
噢 该死
Oh, shit.
我可以进来吗？
Can I come in?
- 你是朱莉娅 对吗？ - 没错
-You're Julia, right? -That's right.
你是哪位？
Who are you?
我是弗兰克
I'm Frank.
我是你丈夫的兄弟.
I'm brother Frank.
噢,对
Oh, yes!
我...我是来参加婚礼的
I--I came for the wedding.
那,我可以进来了吗？
Well, can I come in or not?
对不起,当然可以
I'm sorry. Of course.
热烈欢迎．
You're very welcome.
噢,听你这么说,我很欣慰
Yeah. Well, that's nice to know.
你有毛巾吗？
Do you have a towel?
Have you got a towel?
克里斯蒂！
Kirsty.
浴室里有一条
There's one in the bathroom.
顺便说一句 爸爸有没有告诉你 我已经找到房子了呢？
Oh, by the way, did Daddy tell you I got a room?
房间不大,但挺好.
It's not that big, but it's okay.
朱莉娅
Julia?
我们喝点什么呢？
What shall we drink to?
结婚幸福么？
Wedded bliss?
我很幸福.
I'm very happy
噢,我相信
I'm sure you are.
你得让我吻新娘子
You're gonna let me kiss the bride?
拉里怎么办呢？
What about Larry?
忘了他
Forget him.
朱莉娅...朱莉娅...朱莉娅..
Julia... Julia... Julia...
你得替我分担点重力 我的脚被束住了.
I need to take the weight away from me, my foot's caught.
- 你明白吗？ - 明白了
-You got it? -I got it.
当我拉的时候,你在后面推一下
Now just push it to me as I pull.
这远远不够
It's never enough.
朱莉娅
Julia. Jul...
拜托
Please.
我愿为你做任何事
Ill do anything you want.
任何事
(Whispers) Anything.
这儿
Here.
伤口很深吗？
Oh, is it deep?
不知道,我没有看
I don't know. I haven't looked.
你知道我怕血.
You know me and blood.
- 我快晕倒了． - 你不会晕倒
-I'm gonna faint. -You're not going to faint.
他妈的
Oh, shit!
- 让我看看 - 他妈的．
-Let me see. -Shit!
得去医院缝几针
Oh, it's going to need stitches.
- 但我都快呕吐了． - 你不能吐
-I'm gonna throw up. -You're not going to throw up.
- 放松点儿．放松点儿 - 我都快呕吐了．
-Just take it easy, just take it easy. -I'm gonna throw up.
不会有事儿
It's going to be all right
让我送你去医院
Let's get you to the hospital.
我真是太笨了
So stupid.
怎么啦？
What happened?
只是个小意外.他没事了
It was just an accident. He's all right.
我说,你来开车好吗？ 得去医院给他缝几针
Look, will you drive? He needs stitches.
- 当然可以． - 车钥匙在厨房里
-Yeah, sure. -The keys are in the kitchen.
- 我太笨了． - 不会有事儿
-So stupid. - It's all right.
不不,我真不是开玩笑
No no, I am not kidding.
当时那个医生正在四处闲逛....
This doctor is poking around
就像纳粹集中营里的军医 看见犯人一样兴奋
with all the delicacy and compassion of Josef Mengele,
我警告他: 听着 我要晕过去了喔！
and I'm warning him, : Listen, I'm gonna pass out
他说,噢！你当然不会,老兄
He says, Oh no, of course you're not, old boy. Of course you're not
接下来我倒在地面上...
The next thing you know, I'm on the floor
他傻站在那儿, 好像他才是需要帮助的人
and he's standing there like he's the one who needs help.
可能他是怕你因此而起诉他
He probably is afraid you're gonna sue him.
我应该起诉他
I should do it!
比尔,我应该这样做. 这些事你比较懂吧
Bill, I should do it. You know all about that stuff.
明天我会给你的打电话 我们起诉他吧
I'll call you tomorrow. We'll sue his ass.
这些医生们！
Doctors
没关系,亲爱的
That's right, honey.
我可爱的女儿喝了什么呢？
And what's my darling daughter drinking?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
噢,朱莉娅, 你还想来点白兰地吗？
Listen, Julia, you want some more bubbly?
噢,我不能再喝了 谢谢
Uh no. No more for me, thanks.
好了, 停停停
Okay. Okay, stop
- 我都站不稳了 - 那就躺下好了
-I'm not gonna be able to stand up. -So lie down.
我得先失陪了. 我想我得去睡了
Would you all excuse me? I think I'm going to go to bed.
你还好吗？亲爱的.
-Are you all right, darling? -Uh-huh.
- 我想我们都得到此为止了． - 不行 比尔
-I think we ought to be making a move, too - No Bill!
绝对不行.
Absolutely not!
这是装修工的夜晚
This is the night of the paper hat here.
我们得庆祝一番. 坐下吧
We're celebrating something, so sit down.
晚安.
Good night.
明天晚上你们再来吧
You'll have to come to us next.
对,很快就再见面了. 我希望你们再来
Yeah, real soon. I'm glad you're back.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 晚安 - 晚安
-Good night. -Good night.
- 还痛吗？ - 什么？
-Does it still hurt? -What?
噢,不,只是喝酒时才会如此
No, only when I drink.
噢,我的上帝
Oh, God.
不 拜托
Oh! Christ!
出去！
out！
朱莉娅
Julia.
噢,我的上帝
Oh my God.
不要看着我
Don't look at me.
谁？
Who--
你是谁？
who are you?
我说了,别看着我
I said don't look.
帮我
Help me!
告诉我,你是谁？
Tell me who you are.
我是弗兰克
Frank.
不
No.
No!
相信我,我就是弗兰克
Believe me, it's me.
真的是我
It's really me.
他滴在地板上的血使我又回来了
His blood on the floor, it brought me back.
回来？
Back?
从哪儿回来呢？
From where?
帮我忙,行吗？
Just help me, will you?
拜托了,上帝,帮我
Please, God, help me!
- 有人． - 等等
-Somebody -Wait.
你不能这样离开我. 你不能
You can't leave me like this. You can't.
你想让我做什么呢？
What do you want me to do?
血已经让我恢复到这个程度
The blood brought me this far.
我还要更多的血
I need more.
你得帮我康复
You have to heal me.
嘿.
Hi.
你还吗？
Are you all right?
克里斯蒂？我以为我把你弄丢了.
Kirsty? I thought I'd lost you.
没有,我在这儿
No, I'm here.
晚安
Good night.
你为什么不留在拉里家呢？ 那多有很多房间
So why didn't you stay at Larry's house? There's plenty of room.
噢,那儿是有房间. 但朱莉娅也在那儿
Oh, yeah, there's room, and there's Julia.
噢,我明白了
Ah. I see.
她也像你一样． 那么客套．
She's like you. She's so damn polite.
是吗？ 这有什么问题呢？
Oh, yeah? Meaning what?
我也不知道,她拘谨而冷淡
Oh, I don't know. She's uptight and frigid.
请再说一遍
I beg your pardon.
看到了吧,你就是这样 居然说：请再说一遍
See, there you go. ~ "I beg your pardon."
嘿,我们之间不冷淡吧.
Hey, we're not all frigid.
- 噢 不么？ - 噢 不。
-Oh, no? -Oh, no.
噢,不？
Oh, no?
噢,不
Oh, no.
可我以前都没有 听过别人这样客气说话
That's not what I heard.
那你一定是没有遇到正确的人。
Well, you must have been speaking to all the wrong people.
任何事都可以吗？
Anything?
任何事
Anything.
你会照办吗？
Ycuil do it?
对,我会
Yes... I will.
克里斯蒂?克里斯蒂?
Ki rsty? Ki rsty?
克里斯蒂!
-Kirsty! -Ah!
- 你还好吗？ - 对
-You all right? -Yeah.
我不知道
I don't know.
我在做梦
I--Iwas dreaming.
爸爸
Daddy!
喂
Hello.
我很好,亲爱的.
I'm all right, honey.
我就是想确认一下, 你是否还好
I just wanted to make sure you were okay.
我非常的好
Never better.
- 现在你去好好睡觉吧 - 好
-Now you sleep well, okay? -Yeah.
我爱你,甜心．
I love you, sweetie.
我也爱你,爸爸
I love you too, Daddy.
再见
Bye.
- 是谁呢？ - 她做了一个恶梦
Who was it? -She had a bad dream.
- 谁？ - 克里斯蒂
-Who? -Kirsty.
克里斯蒂
Kirsty.
- 没什么意思 对吗？ - 什么？
-Not much fun, is it? - What?
一个人喝闷酒
Drinking alone.
没什么意思
Not much.
我想也许是吧,嗯
I thought maybe...
对了,
well...
如果我们都没有伴侣 也许我们可以一起喝酒
if we're both on our own, maybe we could have a drink together.
为什么不呢？
Why not?
你得知道,我不是经常...
You know, it's not often that I...
你也知道的
you know.
任何事都有第一次．
There's a first time for everything.
没错儿,对
That's right, yeah.
我想这倒是真的
I suppose that's right.
你要不要....... 来点儿喝的呢？
Would you... like a drink?
噢,不,不
Oh, no no no.
我已经过量了
I'm well over my limit.
你知道 这很有意思,
You know, it's funny,
但是...我..
but I...
我觉得我和你相识了 好几年似的,知道吗？
I feel like I've known you for years, you know?
怎么啦？
What's the matter?
是你带我来这儿的 不是吗？
It's what you brought me here for, isn't it?
噢,不是吗？
Well, isn't it?
我想是这样,对
I suppose so, yes.
那你是怎么回事呢？
So what's your problem?
让我们继续做吧
Let's get on with it.
你他妈不会改变主意吧,对吗？
You're not gonna change your fucking mind, are you?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们到楼上去吧
Let's go upstairs.
好的,好的．对不起,去吧
Okay okay. Sorry, okay? Okay.
好的
Right.
这不是卧室
This isn't the bedroom.
不是
No.
那,这是怎么回事呢？
So what's going on?
没必非要用床,对吗？
We don't need a bed, do we?
是的,没错,我想没必要
Well, no, I suppose not.
我一直喜欢在地板上做.
I've always preferred the floor.
任何事儿都有第一次,对吗？
Oh. First time for everything, eh?
你为什么不...
Why don't you...
把你的夹克脱掉呢？
take your jacket off?
好,为什么不呢
Yeah, why don't I?
你为什么不一起脱？
Why don't you do the same thing?
也许我会的
Maybe I will.
你真是太漂亮了
You're very beautiful.
我漂亮吗？
Am I?
你知道你的美貌.
Oh, you know you are.
你是我见过的 最可爱的女人
Loveliest woman... I've ever seen.
噢,我的上帝
Oh, Christ.
怎么啦？
What's wrong?
等一会儿
Just one minute.
喝了太多的酒
Too much drink.
把膀胱里的水放干
Empty the old bladder.
你锁的门？
Did you lock this?
拜托！拜托了
Please! Please!
别看着我
Don't look at me.
我的上帝
Jesus Christ.
看到了吗？
See?
这再次让我复原了
It's making me whole again.
洒出的每一滴血 都会使我的骨头上增添新肉
Every drop of blood you spill puts more flesh on my bones.
我们都希望这样,不是吗？
And we both want that, don't we?
太好了
Good.
这儿来
Come here.
他妈的过来. 我想抚摸你
Come here, damn you, I wanna touch you.
到爸爸这儿来
Come to Daddy.
朱莉娅
Julia!
Julia.
出来,快出来, 你在哪儿呢？
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
朱莉娅？我在叫你啊. 你听不到吗？
Julia, I was calling for you. Didn't you hear?
你在那儿吗？
Are you in there?
你要吃甜饼吗？亲爱的
You want a cookie, little girl?
我有点不舒服
I'm feeling sick.
噢,宝贝. 我能帮你做点什么呢？
Oh, babe. Is there anything I can get you?
来点白兰地,好吗？
Maybe a--a brandy.
马上就好
It's coming right up.
我很快回来
Ill be down... in a minute.
好的.
Okay.
不必那么急
There's no hurry.
弗兰克
Frank?
我很痛
-Oh. -I'm hurting.
痛？
Hurting?
我的神经开始起作用了
My nerves are beginning to work again.
太好了
Good.
再来一个 也许要两个...
One more, maybe two...
- 没有下次 - 你得让我完全康复
-Not again. -to heal me completely.
这样在他们开始追捕前 我们可以逃走
Then we can be away from here before they start to follow.
- 谁？ - 修道士
-Who? -The Cenobites.
他们发现我只是时间问题... 我得躲开他们
It's only a matter of time before they find I've slipped them.
我必须离开这儿
I must get away from here.
朱莉娅？
Julia?
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
等我一小会儿
Just a moment.
放些音乐,好吗？宝贝
Put on some music. Will you, babe?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
可怜的拉里,还是那么顺从
Poor Larry, obedient as ever.
你小声点儿
Keep your voice down.
不想让你的宝贝听见吗？
Don't want babe to hear.
你很痛
You're hurting.
你不会欺骗我,对吗？
You won't cheat me, will you?
我会跟我在一起 帮助我
You'll stay with me, help me.
这样我们能像以往一样,永远在一起
Then we can be together the way we were before.
现在我们彼此拥有...
We belong to each other now.
同甘 ,共苦
For better, for worse.
唯有真爱
Like love...
至死不渝
only real.
对不起.我是新来的. 你得等等才行
I'm sorry--I'm new here. You're gonna have to wait.
拜托你别乱动,好吗？
Could you not do that, please?
经理在哪儿呢？
Where's the manager?
这的确是个问题 因为他出去吃午餐了
That's a problem too, because he's out to lunch right now.
我想见见负责人
I want to see somebody in charge.
那你得等等才行
Then you're gonna have to wait.
- 抱歉． - 打搅了
-Excuse me. -Well, excuse me!
你在做什么呢？
What are you doing?
快点放回去
Give those back.
噢,我的上帝啊
Oh myGod.
出去.
Get out.
你给我滚出去
You get out of here.
- 嗨 - 嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
刚刚路过, 想看看你下班之后都做些什么
Just came by to see what you're doing after work.
怎么啦？
What's wrong?
- 很古怪的事儿． - 什么？
-Something weird. -What?
没什么
Nothing.
你保证我们不会受到干扰吗？
You're sure we're not gonna be interrupted?
绝对不会
Quite sure.
我只是...
Only I--uh...
我想还是小心点的好
I like to be careful.
我可以品尝到味道了
I can taste that.
我有好长一段时间 品尝不到任何味道
IVs a long time since I tasted anything.
你答应过我,会向我解释
You promised me an explanation.
就是这个
This is it.
- 让我看看． - 不 不要碰它！
-Let me see. -No, don't touch it!
很危险.它能把门打开
It's dangerous. It opens doors.
什么样的门呢？
What kind of doors?
通向快乐的天堂,或者是痛苦的地狱
Doors to the pleasures of heaven or hell.
我已经不在乎是哪个
I didn't care which.
我原以为我已经经历了人生的极限
I thought I'd gone to the limits.
但是 修道士给了我超越了极限的体验
I hadn't. The Cenobites gave me an experience beyond limits.
痛苦与快乐,纠缠交错
Pain and pleasure... indivisible.
他们不能再把我带回去
They won't get me back.
我得活下去,你得帮助我,好吗？
I'm going to live and you're going to help me, yes?
好
Yes.
他们永远也不会找到我
They'll never find us,
在整个茫茫人世
not in the whole wide world.
布恩击中他了.
Boom Boom has got him now!
Boom Boom has got him.
他又被击倒了
He's knocked down again.
我想这些东西使你很厌恶吧
I thought this kind of stuff made you sick.
我看过更糟的
I've seen worse.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
好啊
Fine.
如果你不喜欢, 我们也可以看点别的
Cause we can watch something else
快！干掉他！
Come on! Get him!
噢,不！
Ah! No! No!
那是什么声音？
What was that?
我想我没有把楼上的窗户关好 我去看看
I think I left a window open upstairs. I'll go see.
不用
No.
拉里,那里没什么
Larry! It was nothing.
拉里
Larry!
你到底怎么啦？
What's the matter with you anyway?
只是...是因为我害怕打雷声
It's just that I hate the thunder.
我在这儿
I'm here.
你很安全
You're safe.
你在发抖
You're trembling.
没有什么好怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
你看
Look.
我必须去看看
I really should check it out.
别去那儿,拜托了
Don't go up there, please.
我们一起去吧.来吧
We'll both go up. Come on.
- 拉里 拜托了． - 别担心．来吧
-Larry, please! -Don't worry about it. Come on.
- 别． - 没事的
-Don't. -It's okay. It's okay.
可能是老鼠
It's probably a rat.
我告诉过你
I told you.
没有什么好怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
我们下楼去吧. 我会处理好
Let's go downstairs. I'll make it better.
不要,这儿的光线已经很足了
No, this is enough light.
我们走吧.来吧
Let's go, come on.
我们进里面去
Let's go inside.
好的
Oh, yes.
好的 好的
Yes. Yes.
不
No.
No!
不,拜托了, 不,求你了
No, please don't. No, please!
我受不了,拜托了！
I can't bear it, please!
求你别这样
Please, no!
拜托了
Please!
拜托了,别
Please stop!
我受不了啦！ 拜托你别这样
I can't bear it! Please, no!
我不明白
I don't understand you.
一分钟之前
I mean, one minute...
你比我还亢奋,但接着就...
you're all over me, and the next...
你真让我弄不懂
I just don't understand you.
我也不知道
I don't know.
也许我们不该回这儿
Maybe we shouldn't have come back.
住在布鲁克林绝对不会比这儿更糟
Brooklyn certainly wasn't any worse than this.
听着
Look.
你很爱她 那肯定是她有 值得你爱的地方
You love her, so there must be something worth loving.
我希望问题真的那么简单就好了
I wish it were that simple.
我现在真的有麻烦了,孩子
I've got a real problem here, kiddo.
她甚至不愿离开家门
She doesn't even want to leave the house.
真的吗？
Really?
她好像在...
It's like she's...
等待着什么似的
waiting for something.
是什么？
What?
我不知道
I don't know.
这些我可想不透
It's way beyond me.
听着
Look.
你能.. 你会...
Could you-- would you...
找个时间？
.stop by sometime?
试试跟她交朋友,好吗？
Try to make friends?
当然可以.
Sure.
谁知道呢？ 也许她只是想找个说话的人
Who knows,maybe all she needs is somebody to talk to.
- 你不能爱他 - 你知道的 我不爱他
-You can't love him. -You know I don't.
- 那这有什么妨碍呢？ - 我说了不行
-So where's the harm? -I said no.
那么在修道士来之前 再去找别的人来
Then find me somebody else, before they come looking.
马上
Now!
我...
I... uh...
有时我很孤单
I get lonely sometimes.
人人都是如此
Everybody does.
请进
Come in.
这是什么？
What is this,
做游戏吗？
a game?
我的上帝啊
Jesus Christ!
噢,上帝,救命
Oh, Christ! Help me!
不
Don't!
- 快出去！！ - 求你了
-Get out of here! -Please.
别让他杀我
Don't let him kill me.
救命啊
Help me.
不
No.
- 克里斯蒂 我是弗兰克 弗兰克叔叔 - 不
-Kirsty, it's Frank. It's Uncle Frank. -No!
- 你还记得我吧． - 不
-You remember. -No!
- 到叔叔这儿来 - 放开我！
-Come to Daddy. -Get the fuck off of me!
你长大了, 很漂亮
You've grown. You're beautiful.
别...别碰我
Don't-- don't touch me!
别碰我,救命啊...
Don't touch me or so help mel
你要做什么呢？
What will you do?
你能做什么呢？
What can you do?
没有什么害怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
我敢说,你让你父亲很自豪吧
I bet you make your daddy so proud.
你是这么漂亮
Don't you, beautiful?
怎么会这样！
This isn't happening.
我常常对自己说
I used to tell myself that.
我总是假装自己所承受的痛苦 都只是一场梦
Used to try and pretend I was dreaming all the pain.
但是不要自欺欺人了
But don't you kid yourself.
有些痛苦是人类必须要承受的
Some things have to be endured,
唯有如此, 才能让快乐来的更甜美
and that's what makes the pleasures so sweet.
不
No!
把那个还给我
Give me that!
- 不． - 把它还给我
-No. -Give it to me!
你想要吗？
You want it?
最后一次机会！
One last time:
把那盒子还给我
give me that box.
- 你想要吗？ - 把盒子还给我！
-You want it? -Give me the box!
你想要吗？他妈的！
You want it? Fucking have it!
不
No!
克里斯蒂
Kirsty.
到我这儿来
(Echoes) Come to Daddy.
我是弗兰克 你记得吧.
It's Frank. You remember.
我是弗兰克叔叔
It's  Uncle Frank.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
你醒了
You're awake.
- 好孩子． - 出什么事了？
-Good girl. -What happened?
- 我去叫医生 - 等等 我怎么会在这儿呢？
-I'll get the doctor. -Wait a minute. How did I get here?
我不会用很长时间
I won't be a moment.
拜托,回床上去
Please, get back into bed.
我得给我爸爸打电话.
I have to call my father.
这个很容易安排 但首先得回床上去.
That's easily arranged, but first, back into bed.
这很重要,真的很重要
It's important. It really is--
重要的事情先来
First things first.
我和你谈过之后, 我们会让你打电话
We'll get you a telephone after we've talked.
这是什么？是音乐盒吗？
What about this? Ring any bells?
你紧紧地抓着它不放
You were hanging onto it like grim death.
我不记得了.
I don't remember.
好了,警察想跟你淡淡 你也知道吧
Well, the police will want to speak to you. -You know that.
噢,我的上帝
Oh, Christ.
另外,也许这个能让你记起来吧
In the meantime, maybe this will jog your memory.
他妈的
Shit.
快打开！
Open!
噢,开门啊
Oh, come on!
你打开了盒子,
The box. You opened it,
我们就来了
we came.
这只是个游戏盒子
It's just a puzzle box!
噢,不.
Oh, no.
这意味着你召唤了我们
It is a means to summon us.
你是谁？
Who are you?
是未来世界的探险家
Explorers in the further regions of experience:
是某些人眼中的魔鬼 某些人眼中的天使
demons to some, angels to others.
这只是个误会
It was a mistake!
我不...我并不想把它打开的
I didn't--I didn't mean to open it!
这只是个误会
It was a mistake!
你们可以...回到地狱
You can all... go to hell!
不行.不能没有收获就离开
We can't. Not alone.
你启动了盒子.
You solved the box,
所以我们才来的 现在你得跟我们走
we came. Now you must come with us.
体会我们的快乐
Taste our pleasures
求你们走吧,放了我吧
Please, go away and leave me alone!
噢,请别流泪
Oh, no tears, please.
这是对美好磨难的一种浪费
It's a waste of good suffering.
等等！等等！等等！ 拜托你们等等
Wait! Wait! Wait! Please, wait!
没有争辩的时间了.
No time for argument.
这样的事以前 你们也做过,对吗？
You've done this before, right?
很多很多次了
Many, many times.
你们知道一个叫 弗兰克.科顿的男人吗？
To a man called Frank Cotton?
认得
Oh, yes.
他从你们手里跑掉了
He escaped you.
- 没人可以从我们这儿逃走． - 他逃了 我见过他的
Nobody escapes us. He did. I've seen him.
- 不可能！ - 他还活着
- Impossible. -He's alive!
即使他从我们手中逃脱
Supposing he had escaped us.
那又关你什么事呢？
What has that to do with you?
我可以... 我可以带你们去找他
I--I can-- I can lead you to him,
你们可以带他走,而不是我
and you can take him back instead of me.
也许我们更喜欢你
Perhaps we'd prefer you.
我想听到他的认罪
I want to hear him confess himself,
也许
then maybe...
maybe.
但如果你敢骗我们...
But if you cheat us...
我们会把你的灵魂撕裂
We'll tear your soul apart.
她会把一切告诉他们.
She'll tell them everything.
我想不会 她会先去提醒拉里
I don't think so. She'll want to warn Larry first.
现在也许是她了
That's probably her now...
- 或者是警察 - 那没有任何区别
-or the police. -It doesn't make any difference.
你不担心吗？
Don't you care?
我在乎的是新的肌肤
What I care about is a new skin.
也许我们得离开．
Maybe we should just leave.
像这样离开吗？看看我
Like this? Look at me.
我们不能留在这儿
We can't just stay here.
我兄第马上就会回家
My brother will be home soon.
怎么啦？
What is it?
我不知从何说起
I don't know where to begin.
你在说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
你最好自己看看吧
It's best you see for yourself.
我让她安稳地呆在这儿.
I left her here safe and sound.
我甚至把门都锁上了
I even locked the door.
但她现在不在这儿了
Well, she's not here now.
我也在找她
I'll start looking for her.
也许她回...
Maybe she's gone back to...
回她爸爸家去了
to her father's house.
爸爸？
Daddy?
爸爸,是我！克里斯蒂. 让我进去
Daddy, it's me, it's Kirsty! Let me in!
爸爸,让我进来吧
Daddy, let me in!
- 克里斯蒂 很晚了 - 我爸爸在哪儿呢？
-Kirsty? It'ss very late. -Where is my dad?
- 出什么事了？ - 我想见我爸爸
-What's the matter? -I want to see my father!
当然可以
Of course.
他在哪儿？
Where is he?
爸爸
Daddy?
- 爸爸！你还好吗？ - 我当然好 我当然好
-Daddy, you're okay. You're all right. -Sure I am. I am.
- 你没事吧． - 没事儿
-You're okay! -It's okay.
我真怕你出意外
I was so afraid that something happened to you.
我知道.我知道
I know, I know.
我得跟你淡淡．
I need to talk to you.
当然可以
Yeah. Of course.
好了,宝贝. 朱丽娅把一切都告诉我了
It's okay, baby. Julia told me everything.
噢,不,你得明白...
Oh, no, see...
你兄第弗兰克在楼上
your brother Frank is upstairs.
他住在楼上 他想要你的命
He's upstairs and he's trying to kill you.
- 他会杀了你！ - 等等 等等 等等
-He's gonna kill you! -No, wait, wait, wait.
弗兰克做的事儿真是可怕极了
Whatever Frank did was unspeakable.
真是可怕极了
Unspeakable.
但你得相信我
But believe me,
一切都结束了
it's finished with now.
为什么结束了呢？
Why is it finished?
他没了
He's gone.
"没了" 是什么意思？
What does 'gone' mean?
他死了,克里斯蒂
He's dead, Kirsty.
他是个疯子,宝贝.
He was insane, baby.
他是条疯狗,我得帮他结束悲剧
A mad dog. I had to put him out of his misery.
我的上帝,多惨的场面
Jesus, what a scene.
等我感觉好点以后
And when I'm feeling better,
我会报警并向他们说明白
Ill go to the police and try to make them understand.
这恐怕只有上帝明白了
God knows...
我自己都想不明白怎么回事
I don't really understand myself.
他有没有伤害你？宝贝
Did he hurt you, baby?
没有,我很好
No, I'm okay.
他死了更好,我可怜的弗兰克
He's better off dead. Poor Frank.
真是让我难以置信.
I don't believe this.
- 真是让我难以置信 - 相信这一切吧
-I don't believe this. -Believe it.
我得看看他
I need to see him.
- 不行 没必要了． - 不 我要看！
-No, you don't. -Yes, I do.
必须！
Yes.
带她去看看
Show her.
我要找干这事儿的男人
We want the man who did this.
不.
No.
不, 这不是咱们说好的
No, that wasn't the deal.
那是我父亲,你们不能抓他
He's my father and you can't have him.
不要！
No!
啊！让开！
Ah! Move.
克里斯蒂
Kirsty...
让开
Move!
怎么啦？
What's the matter?
没时间了
There's no time.
我告诉你了,现在一切都结束了
Wait, no wait. I told you all that's over with now.
不,还没有. 我们得离开这儿
No, it's not! We've got to get out of here!
不,跟我们呆在一起
No, stay with us.
我们会很开心
We can all be happy here.
不
No.
到爸爸这儿来
Come to Daddy.
我的上帝
Oh my God!
来...
Come...
爸爸这儿来
to Daddy.
弗兰克
-Ah! -Frank!
好吧
Well...
猫与老鼠的游戏 到此为止了
so much for the catand-mouse shit!
不
No!
不是我
Not me!
要不徇私情,宝贝
It's nothing personal, baby.
你在哪儿？美人儿
Where are you, beautiful?
出来,出来,不论你在哪儿
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
老天
Oh my God.
爸爸,爸爸
Daddy.
不要,别为他而悲伤了
No, don't mourn him.
在我们触到他之前, 他就已经被吓死了
He was dead long before we ever touched him.
- 杂种！ - 安静点儿
-Bastard! -Hush now.
一切都很完美.
Everything's all right.
弗兰克在这儿
Frank's here.
杂种！
Bastard!
你亲爱的弗兰克叔叔
Your dear old Uncle Frank.
这是怎么回事？
What the hell is that?
弗兰克
Frank.
不！
No!
我们得听到你的亲口忏悔
We had to hear it from your own lips.
这并非是做给你看的
This isn't for your eyes.
你给我下圈套
You set me up,
婊子！
bitch!
上帝也要流泪
Jesus wept
不会这么快离开我们,对吗？
Not leaving us so soon, are you?
我们还有好多景色要给你看
We have such sights to show you.
噢,他妈的
Oh, shit.
- 不！不要这样做 - 去地狱吧
-No! Don't do that! -Go to hell!
克里斯蒂
Kirsty!
不
No.
史蒂夫
Steve.
不!
No!
他妈的！
Oh, shit!
噢,克里斯蒂 谢天谢地,你还好.
Oh, Kirsty! Thank God you're okay.
我们马上离开这个鬼地方
Let's get the hell out of here! Now!
噢,不
Oh, no.
噢,上帝.不
Oh, God. No.
打开
Open!
史蒂夫！不要
Steve! No!
你想要什么？先生
What's your pleasure, sir?